JUSTINE STROUP

DEVELOPER

CONTACT ☐ 719-287-6339 ☑ justinejohanna04@gmail.com ⊕ www.justinestroup.dev ☐ github.com/justinestroup17 TECHNOLOGIES

- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- SQL
- Git
- Microsoft Excel

WORK EXPERIENCE

Healthcare Medical Waste Services, LLC

Accounting Clerk

2022 - Current

- Data analysis: create data reports to assist company in making clientbased decisions.
- Demonstrate advanced excel skills in reporting and show findings to president.

AAA Colorado

Emergency Roadside Dispatcher

2018 - 2022

- Dispatched trucks with urgency to members in emergency roadside situations.
- Used quick-decision making skills to prioritize levels of emergency based on members' safety.
- Facilitated members in benefits of membership products and services.

SUMMARY

Fourth year computer science major with a keen eye for detail and a strong passion for tackling complex problems. With over six years of active development experience, I am eager to secure a position in a technology-driven industry.

EDUCATION

Fort Hays State University, Bachelor's of Science in Computer Science

August 2019 - May 2024

- Relevant coursework: data structures and algorithms, object-oriented programming, full-stack web development, software development and methodologies, and database design & programming.
- GPA 3.81

Colorado Technical University, Associate's of Science in Information Technology, *summa cum laude*

November 2017 - October 2018

- Relevant coursework: computer security, operating systems, information technology, and networking.
- GPA 4.0

PROJECTS

Project #1: justinestroup.dev

Developed my portfolio from scratch using various development tools such as HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript to showcase my projects.

Project #2: Study Companion App

Developed a web-application designed to assist students in mastering crucial terminology and concepts, thereby enhancing their success in their academic endeavors.

Project #3: ATM Banking Program

Developed a command-line interface program in JAVA using OOP principles and exception handling that allows users to deposit and withdraw from a mock bank account and view their account summary.